citybase.com 2004-10-10

# privacy

| 

## Citybase.com Privacy Program   
  
---  
**Privacy Policy (Effective May 12, 2004)**  
Citybase.com is proud to be a member of the Trip Network. Citybase.com is committed to protecting your privacy while you are visiting our Site. Rest assured -- you're in control at Citybase.com.

In order to provide the best in customer service, we may ask you to share "personal information" -- information unique to you, such as your name, address, and phone number. First and foremost, we want you to understand our policy regarding the collection and use of your personal information.  

 **The Personal Information Collected**  
You may visit our Site or call Customer Service to search for great travel deals without providing us with any personal information.

  *  **Personal Information**  
We offer you the flexibility and freedom to complete a travel-related purchase on our Site at any time, and establishing a Personal Account with us is so easy to do. When you create your Personal Account, you will be asked to share with us certain basic personal information, such as your name, e-mail address, and password. Should you choose to do so, you can supplement the basics with your credit card number, travel preferences, and more. After creating your Personal Account, you can visit or update the personal information in your Account at any time. By completing and updating your personal information, you help us tailor our services to better meet your needs.
  *  **Transaction Information**  
In order to complete a travel-related purchase, you will be asked to share with us information required to complete the transaction successfully, such as billing address, credit card number and expiration date, etc.

 **How Personal Information Is Used**  
When you establish your Personal Account or make travel arrangements on our Site, we use your personal information in the following ways: 

  * When you make travel arrangements, your personal information will be shared with all third-party vendors necessary to successfully complete the transaction -- including the vendors you have selected (for example, hotels) and others who facilitate the transaction (for example, credit card authorization companies).
  * From time to time, you may receive communications from us, including: (i) specific information we want to communicate to you regarding your travel arrangements; (ii) notifications regarding updates or modifications to our Site; and (iii) details regarding any special promotions sponsored by us, such as any rebates, sweepstakes and gift promotions. These communications may be sent by us or by third parties performing services on our behalf.
  * You may also choose to receive from us, or trustworthy third parties acting on our behalf, special promotions that we believe will be valuable to you, including e-mails promoting special travel deals, sponsored by us or third party vendors. To subscribe or unsubscribe to these types of communications, you may modify your Personal Account at any time.
  * From time to time, in an effort to improve our service, we may ask third parties to conduct marketing-research analyses on our behalf and, as such, the information we provide to them is restricted to marketing-research analyses only. Any personal information we provide to such third parties is protected under confidentiality agreements.
  * We may disclose your personal information (i) if you fail to pay amounts due for travel products or services; or (ii) if you violate our Terms of Use or any governmental, regulatory or other enforcement agency law, rule, or regulation. Unless otherwise prohibited by law or our contractual obligations, we may disclose personal information if required to do so by law, court order, or as requested by a governmental or law enforcement authority, or in the good faith believe that disclosure is otherwise necessary or advisable. Such situations may include: to perform, maintain or enforce contracts with our customers; to protect our rights or properties and those of our business affiliates, customers, employees or others; or when we have reason to believe that disclosing the information is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may be causing, or who may be threatening to cause, interference with or damage to our rights or properties, whether intentionally or otherwise; or when anyone else could be harmed by such activities.
  * In the event that our Company or this Site or certain of our assets are acquired, your personal information may be one of the transferred assets.

Use of your personal information by third parties distributing promotions on our behalf shall be subject to our Privacy Policy.  
  
 **What We Won't Do With Personal Information**  
Citybase.com will not sell or rent your personal information to any third parties.  
 **Security**  
Because security is important to us, we exercise great care in providing secure transmission of your personal information before it is transferred across the Internet from your personal computer to our secure servers. We use industry-standard, secure-socket-layer (SSL) technology, which is utilized by most popular browsers, including Netscape and Microsoft Explorer, to encrypt (or convert into code) your personal information before it is transferred across the Internet. To further safeguard your most sensitive credit card information, we transfer such information across the Internet in an encrypted format and then store such information in our secure database.

Your personal information is password-protected. If you ever forget your password, we will help you create a new one. Remember to sign out of your account and close your browser window when you have finished visiting our Site in order to ensure that others cannot access your personal information.

We will permit only authorized employees, who are trained in the proper handling of personal data, to access your personal information.

To further protect your personal information, we have a security system that includes: world-class firewall technologies; logical network segmentation, allowing restricted access to stored profile information; and logical and physical security restrictions to our databases and systems.  
  
 **Other, Non-Personal Information Collected**  
Like many other Internet sites, we automatically collect non-personal information regarding our visitors, such as software client information (for example, IP addresses, browser versions and operating systems) and aggregate information (for example, number of pages accessed) in order to analyze Web traffic and usage trends. Information of this nature does not pertain to your specific identity and is not associated with your personal information.

To enhance your experience on our Site, we and our third-party advertiser(s) commonly employ Internet technologies, such as "cookies," to collect and store non-personal information about our visitors. "Cookies" are small pieces of information that are transferred by a website and stored by your Web browser on your computer's hard drive. With most browsers, you can set the preferences to show a warning each time a cookie request is received. You can also set the browser not to accept cookies at all. However, because we won't be able to personalize your experience if we cannot recognize you, we suggest that you allow your browser to accept cookies.

Cookies and Web beacons (also called "pixel tags") may be used by us or our third-party advertiser(s) to determine how you reached our Site, to track your usage patterns once you are on our Site, and to target our Internet banner advertisements on our Site and other websites. For more information about our third-party advertiser(s), cookies, and how to opt out, please [click here](http://www.doubleclick.net/us/corporate/privacy).  
  
 **What Is Not Covered By This Privacy Policy**  
Except as covered above, this Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices or policies of any companies or entities that we do not own or control, including links to sites that are not maintained by us, or to people that we do not employ or manage. Because these companies or entities may have privacy policies that differ from this Privacy Policy, please be sure to review their respective privacy policies before providing them with any personal information.  
 **Questions, Comments or Concerns**  
If you have additional questions or concerns regarding our Privacy Policy, please e-mail us at [ldc-privacy@lodging.com](mailto:ldc-privacy@lodging.com).  
 **Privacy Policy Updates**  
We may, in our sole discretion, revise this Privacy Policy at any time; all such revisions shall be effective when posted. If we change the way your personal information will be used, we will post an announcement on our homepage. We encourage you to periodically review this Privacy Policy in order to keep apprised of our current privacy practices.  
---  
Top | [Online Reservations](http://info.citybase.com/affiliates/us_reservations.cgi?remote=citybase&isolatenetrate=true) | [Hot Hotel Deals](http://info.citybase.com/hot-deals.cgi?remote=citybase) | [City Guides](http://www.citybase.com/travelguides.htm) | [Customer Service](http://www.citybase.com/info.html) | [Air](http://www.cheaptickets.com/trs/lodgingcom/flight_services/fare_grouped_search.xsl) | [Car](http://www.cheaptickets.com/trs/lodgingcom/car_services/car_search.xsl) | [Cancel Reservation](http://hotels.hotel-helpline.com/servlet/Cancellation?remote=citybase) | Home
